sunshineapp.com 2017-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Sunshine

This "Privacy Policy" describes how SunShine collects, processes and protects your personal information. SunShine's Privacy Policy applies to all Services provided by SunShine or SunShine's Subsidiaries (as described in more detail in SunShine Service Terms and Conditions) and any Services or products that display or refer to this Privacy Policy, regardless of whether you use the Services through SunShine's website, your mobile phone, mobile device, TV, PC or any other equipment suitable to use the Services. 

###### 1\. Why, how and what personal information we collect about you

You can generally use parts of our Services or our website without giving us any personal information about you. However, most of our Services and parts of our website(services) are only accessible if you register a MEMBER account with SERVICE and complete and submit the information required for the registration process. For this purpose we may request you to provide us with personal information about you which may comprise your name, address, phone number and(or) email address, details of your visits to our Services or website or other information specifically required to offer our Services to you. We collect this information about you when you submit it through our Services or website, typically when you register your MEMBER account or when email us or correspond with us. Some of the personal information that we collect about you will be "Personal Data". This means information and data related to you and which may be used to identify you. 

###### 2\. How we use your Personal Data

We use your Personal Data where this is required to provide our Services or parts thereof (including our website) to you and generally to fulfill our contractual obligations towards you. In particular, we may use your Personal Data for any of the following purposes, provided that this is permissible under applicable law: 

  1. to register you and to enable you to use our Services or website;
  2. to administer our Services or website (including any searches or requests for information about our products or Services);
  3. for assessment and analysis of our market, customers, products and services, including asking you for your opinions on our products and Services and carrying out customer surveys;
  4. to enable us to monitor, review and improve the products and services which we offer;
  5. for internal record keeping;
  6. to consider employing you if you have provided information in an application for a position with us; and
  7. to review the SERVICE and third party services you have used and to recommend similar services to you.

To the extent permissible pursuant to applicable law, (a) we may combine the Personal Data that we collect about you through our Services or website with information that you provide to us by other means and (b) we may store that information together in a combined database or in separate databases. We will not retain your Personal Data for longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it was intended or initially collected, or as required under any contract with you or by applicable law. We will delete your Personal Data once you inform us that you will no longer be using our Services unless and to the extent we are required to retain your Personal Data for legitimate reasons (e.g. due to legal requirements or if we still need your Personal Data to process the contractual relationship with you, such as billing or accounting) or if a deletion of your Personal Data would only be possible with unreasonable efforts, in which case we will lock your Personal Data instead of a deletion. We will not collect an excessive amount of Personal Data about you or any information that is not relevant to the purposes it was collected for. 

###### 3\. Direct Marketing

We may use your Personal Data for marketing purposes, in particular to display to you or present you with advertisements and promotion materials, to inform you about our products or to conduct free prize draws and prize competitions and other such information which we believe may be of interest to you based on your use of and your interests in our Services, always provided that such use complies with applicable laws. We will only send you any advertisement, marketing or promotional material or product information, if you have elected to receive such information by email and/or post when you completed the registration process. Depending on the jurisdiction you reside in and in accordance with applicable laws in your country we may ask you to expressly consent to such use before we send you any marketing or promotional material or before we send you any product information. You can change your mind about your preferences in respect of direct marketing at any time by using the unsubscribe information on every such mailing. by contacting us (see below for details on how to contact us). If you do so, we would not remove your Personal Data from our database(s) to the extent that this Personal Data is still required by us under the terms of this Privacy Policy or to continue to provide our Services to you. 

###### 4\. Location-based services

Some of our Services, for example the "Find My Mobile" service, make use of and require you to provide us with location-based data ("Location-Based Services"). The Location-Based Services are offered by collecting, storing, transmitting or processing location data of your device. SERVICE will only process any location-based data when you consent to such use, typically when you register for the respective Location-Based Service. Location-based data is generally anonymous and does not personally identify you. However, the information gathered by locating your device may be combined with your Personal Data in order for us to provide you with the Location-Based Services, such as Remote Locator and Phone Tracking. All such information will be dealt with in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

###### 5\. Sharing of your Personal Information

We will not share or disclose your Personal Data to any third party (including SERVICE 's Subsidiaries) without your consent, except (a) where this is necessary in order to provide our Services to you, (b) to pursue our legitimate interests or (c) if we are required to disclose your Personal Data in order to comply with any legal obligation or the decision of a judicial authority or (d) where we are otherwise permitted to do so by applicable law. We will never share your Personal Data with third parties if this is not permissible under applicable law. You acknowledge that any Personal Data that you submit to our Services or website which is typically visible to others (e.g. blogs, forums and discussion pages) may result in such information being published and being visible to others. You should take common sense precautions about the Personal Data you provide in such environments and acknowledge that your Personal Data will be published in such a way for others to see. Accessing your information/ Your California Privacy Rights

Under the laws of some jurisdictions, you may have the right to request details of your Personal Data which we collect. If permitted by law, we may charge you a small fee for providing you with such information. If you would like to make any such request, please contact our customer service department at the email address provided below.

California residents are entitled once a year, free of charge, to request and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of Personal Data to third parties for their direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2013 will receive information about 2012 sharing activities). As set forth in this Privacy Policy, we comply with this law by offering our visitors the ability to tell us not to share your Personal Data with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, consistently exercise your opt-out choice whenever you provide Personal Data to us or send an e-mail to opt-out-shine-the-light-[support@sunshineapp.com](mailto:support@sunshineapp.com) SERVICE may need to ask you to provide follow-up information in order to duly process your e-mail request.

Please help us to ensure that your information is accurate and up to date. If you think that any of your information is incorrect or incomplete, please write to our customer service department. 

###### 6\. Security

We are committed to ensure that your Personal Data is kept and stored securely and we maintain reasonable physical, technical and organisational measures and procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect through our Services and our website. This has been done with a view to preventing unauthorised or unlawful processing of your Personal Data and accidental, unauthorised or unlawful access, use, processing, copying, alteration, transfer, loss or destruction of, or damage to your Personal Data. Whilst we have done all of this, and comply with the standards required by applicable laws, we cannot guarantee that your Personal Data is secure when submitted or otherwise communicated through insecure means. We protect the security of your Personal Data by: 

  1. using encryption where appropriate;
  2. limiting access to your Personal Data (for example, only our staff or employees who need access to it for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy will have access to it).

However, these measures do not release you from taking appropriate steps to keep your Personal Data safe and secure, in particular by avoiding obvious MEMBER ID's or passwords, by ensuring that you do not disclose your password(s) or grant any other person access to your MEMBER account and your Personal Data. 

###### 7\. Links to external content resources

Our Services or website may link or direct you to other websites, services or external content resources which are outside of our control. Whilst we try to ensure that we link or direct you only to services or websites that share our privacy and security standards, once you have left our Services or our website we cannot safeguard and are not responsible for the protection and privacy of any Personal Data which you provide on other websites. You should exercise caution and review the privacy statement applicable to the respective service or website. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for those policies. 

###### 8\. Web tracking (cookies and web beacons)

We use cookies (small text files that store information on your hard drive) for certain functions and operations of our Services or website. Cookies help us to understand which sections of our Services or website are the most popular because they allow us to see which pages or Services visitors are accessing and how much time they are spending on them. By studying these we are able to adapt our Services or website to suit your demands and to provide you with a more customised user experience. For example, cookies allow us to ensure that the information displayed on your next visit or login will match your MEMBER preferences. You may configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. For example, on Microsoft Internet Explorer you can disable or delete cookies by selecting "Tools/Internet Options". Please note that our Services and our website are designed to work with cookies and disabling cookies may affect your usage of our Services or our website and may prevent you from taking full advantage of our Services. We do not exchange cookies with any third party websites or external data suppliers, except with third parties working with us to provide our Services to you. Our Services or website and the communications generated from using and/or registering to our Services or website, such as promotional emails, may contain electronic images known as "web beacons". Web beacons generally work in conjunction with cookies, and we may use them in the same way we use cookies (see above). 

###### 9\. Changes to this Privacy Policy

SERVICE may change and update this Privacy Policy from time to time. SERVICE will notify you of any material changes or additions to this Privacy Policy and will provide you with a copy of the amended Privacy Policy, either under this http://www.sunshineapp.com by use of your email address provided to SERVICE or by any other suitable means which ensure that you will be able to take notice of the changes to this Privacy Policy. 

###### 10\. Accessing and correcting your Personal Data

You can access, review at any time by logging into your MEMBER account and visiting your MEMBER profile. Once you have access to your MEMBER profile you can review any Personal Data you provided to us when you registered to our Services or to our website. See the help section on our website to learn more on how to access your account and how to edit your MEMBER profile or correct your Personal Data. Alternatively, you can contact us directly to learn about what Personal Data we have stored about you and how to correct any of your Personal Data. 

###### 11\. How to contact us with regard to your Personal Data

You can contact us at [support@sunshineapp.com](mailto:support@sunshineapp.com) to learn more about our commitment to privacy and this Privacy Policy. Under certain jurisdictions and data protection laws you may have the right to request details of Personal Data which we hold about you or to request the correction or deletion of your Personal Data. Please contact us at privacy. [sunshine@sunshineapp.com](mailto:sunshine@sunshineapp.com) for this purpose or alternatively contact our customer services department (which is accessible through the help menu on our website).Please help us to ensure that the information that we hold about you is accurate and up to date. If you think that any information we have stored about you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us at privacy. [sunshine@sunshineapp.com](mailto:sunshine@sunshineapp.com) write to our customer services department. 

Sunshine Privacy Policy (09-May-2016 Ver. 1.2)
